<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eric's ML Playground</title>
    <description>This is the blog of ML newbie. Maybe you will see very rubish codes but please let me know the better ways. Thank you!
</description>
    <link>http://fallen32.github.io/MLplayground/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://fallen32.github.io/MLplayground/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 01:09:42 +0900</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 01:09:42 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jekyll in Windows: I took a week to install Jekyll</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Ok, I took a week to install Jekyll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll is a good static site generator(Am I right?). It is easy to install with good other blogs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I spend a week. Let me share my failure experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I tried to use Jekyll-theme-slate. This Theme is uncommon which does not make a post in _post/. 
I think this is the theme for really simple site which contains only informations about certain project. 
Therefore, if you want to run a blog, then please do not use theme-slate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may see some recommendations of jekyll themes. Try them and save your time :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, for window users, I summarize how I install jekyll with Contrarium themes in below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Install git or github, use git-bash as your default git editor.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Install ruby 2.4.x with ruby installer. Dev kit will pop-up after ruby install. Don’t kill it.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Install Dev kit called MSYS2 with MINGW64 or MINGW32. (if you skip this, Make error will appears during jekyll installation.)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Download contrarium themes and use it as skeleton.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Open your git editor, type ‘gem install bundler’ then type ‘bundler install’&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Connect your git repository to remote repository.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Check in local using ‘bundle exec jekyll serve’&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe I miss some steps. If you have problems with these steps, please send me a email and let’s solve it TOGETHER!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>http://fallen32.github.io/MLplayground/jekyll/2017/12/21/FirstJekyll.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://fallen32.github.io/MLplayground/jekyll/2017/12/21/FirstJekyll.html</guid>
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
